Start the holidays on a high note.
Zoey's Extraordinary Christmas is a tv movie, comedy,
music film directed by Richard Shepard.
On her first holiday without her father, Zoey attempts to create a magical
Christmas for her family just like the ones Mitch used to do.
Zoey Clarke, played by Jane Levy.
Max Richman, played by Skylar Astin.
Mo, played by Alex Newell.
Simon Haynes, played by John Clarence Stewart.
David Clarke, played by Andrew Leeds.
Emily Kang, played by Alice Lee.
Zoey's Extraordinary Playlist is an American jukebox musical comedy-drama television
series created by Austin Winsberg that premiered on January 7, 2020, on NBC.
The series stars Jane Levy as Zoey Clarke, a software developer who discovers she
has the ability to hear the innermost thoughts of people as songs.
Each episode features multiple song-and-dance numbers that develop the
storyline, with each cast member singing their own character's songs.
Except for the season 2 song "Crimson Love," the soundtrack
consists entirely of previously written popular songs.
The series also stars Skylar Astin, Alex Newell, John Clarence Stewart, Peter Gallagher, Mary Steenburgen, Lauren
Graham, Andrew Leeds, Alice Lee, Michael Thomas Grant and Kapil Talwalkar, and Bernadette Peters.
In June 2020, the series was renewed for a second
season which premiered on January 5, 2021.
In June 2021, the series was canceled after two seasons.
In 2021, streaming service The Roku Channel released
an original two-hour holiday film.
In addition to songs performed on Zoey's Extraordinary Christmas, the second original song in the series — "North Star", written
by Mary Steenburgen, Caitlyn Smith and Troy Verges and sung by Tori Kelly — played during the end credit sequence.
The film explores themes of holiday, family, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.